

KEY SKILLS

Web technologies:

Front-end:

- HTML5.
- CSS3 & SASS.
- Bootstrap.
- Google Material Design.
- JavaScript.
- jQuery.
- React.js
- Vue.js

Back-end:

- PHP.
- Laravel.
- Node.js
- Express.js
- REST APIs.
- -OutSystems.
- Mobile development:
 - -React Native.
 - -OutSystems.
- Database and ORM:
 - SQL.
 - NoSQL.
- Versioning and Control:
 - Git.
 - GitHub/BitBucket.
- Tools:
 - Adobe Photoshop.
 - Adobe Xd.

Yaser M. Saleh

Software Engineer

Mobile: +962790809202

Email: YaserMuhammedJaser@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/yasersaleh/

Portfolio: https://yasermj.github.io/yaser/

OBJECTIVE

An ambitious Software Engineer specialized in web development with a sense of simplicity and creativity that has effectively prototype and developed responsive user pleasuring products. A regular volunteer and a participant in IT events and meetups.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer – NESMA

Mar 2020 - Present

Full web and mobile enterprise applications development and automation using latest development platforms.

• GIS Developer – InfoGraph

Jan 2020 – Feb 2020

Esri ArcGIS based mapping and infographic web solutions implementation and integration.

EDUCATION

Coding Academy by Orange

June 2019 – Dec 2019

One of the top trainees with high evaluation scores and 10+ practical projects. Actively leading, planning and coming up with agile creative ideas.

• B.Sc. degree – Computer Science:

2015 – 2019

- Al Hussein bin Talal University.
- Ranked #1 on CS 2015 and #3 on the IT college -2019.
- GPA &Rating: 79 Very good.

• General Secondary certificate – IT Stream:

2012 - 2013

- Rosary Sisters School.
- GPA: 77.